Daniel Cannon Smith

281.391.9630 Houston.TX

Email: dancannon27@icloud.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dancannon27/Github: https://github.com/Dancannon27

A Junior Web Developer that has served in the US Navy for six years, supported Operation Enduring Freedom as well as operations involving protecting nuclear weapons at sea. After military separation Daniel pursued the entertainment industry for audio design. While earning that degree he delivered for a food service website and operated dispatch via web application. Today he is a school bus driver looking to find a more challenging career as a web developer.

Skills & Tools:

Web Development

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Design, Bootstrap, Handlebars, Cookies/Local Storage, React.js, Node.js, Express, Security and Session Storage, User Authentication, MySQL, MongoDB

Advanced skills using the following Audio and Video editing software: Pro Tools, Logic Pro, Final Cut Pro

Work Experience:

School Bus Driver – Katy I.S.D. – Katy, TX 281.396.7560 (Supervisor: Kale McKisson) November 2016 – Present

Delivery Driver/Dispatcher –
Bringittome.com – San Diego, CA 619.821.8182 (Owner: Sherry Nep)
August 2014 – April 2016

Steam Turbine Mechanic/Nuclear Weapons Security Guard – US Navy (DD-214 upon request) April 2004 – April 2010

Education:

University of Texas-Austin Certificate in Web Development - Grad: 03/24/18

The Art Institute of California- San Diego Bachelor of Science in Audio Production – Grad: 03/24/16